{
    "subject": "resource/The_Gambler_(2014_film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:2014_films",
    "human_readable": "The Gambler (2014 film) is about 2014 films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9269870519638062,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'The Gambler' (2014)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9026708602905273,
            "question": "Is there a specific actor who starred in the 2014 version of 'The Gambler'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8622604608535767,
            "question": "Are there any famous films with the same title as 'The Gambler' (2014)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.834108293056488,
            "question": "What are some other films similar to 'The Gambler' (2014)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6953299641609192,
            "question": "Would you recommend watching 'The Gambler' (2014)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6387775540351868,
            "question": "What is the main topic of the film 'The Gambler'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6329296827316284,
            "question": "Has 'The Gambler' (2014) received any major awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5401784181594849,
            "question": "What year was the film 'The Gambler' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.453604519367218,
            "question": "What is a common theme explored in films about gamblers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2394079715013504,
            "question": "What makes a good film about gambling?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Gambler (2014 film) is about 2014 films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6234_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is a common theme explored in films about gamblers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6234_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the film 'The Gambler' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6234_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has 'The Gambler' (2014) received any major awards?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6234_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6234_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6234_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6234_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6234_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6234_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6234_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6234_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6234_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6234_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6234_58.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe phrase \"The Gambler (2014) is a remake of the classic 1974 film of the same name\" and details about its release in 2014 support that The Gambler (2014 film) is indeed about 2014 films."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\"output\": \"no\"}\n\nThe query \"The Gambler (2014 film) is about 2014 films\" does not make sense in the context of the documents provided. The documents discuss the 2014 remake of \"The Gambler,\" which is based on a previous work, but they do not indicate that the movie itself is about other films from 2014. Thus, the information given does not support this claim."
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided context discusses the 2014 film \"The Gambler\"  in relation to a 1974 film of the same name and its literary inspiration, suggesting it's about the themes and narrative present in the film rather than simply being a factual statement about its release year.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because the 2014 film \"The Gambler\" is actually a remake of the 1974 film, not about 2014 films.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}